{
    "china_history" : [
        {
            "type": "short_answer",
            "prompt": "What is the book of Confucius' sayings, compiled by his followers, called??",
            "correct_answer": "The Analects"
        },
        {
            "type": "short_answer",
            "prompt": "What was the earliest recorded ruling dynasty of China?",
            "correct_answer": "Shang"
        },
        {
            "type": "short_answer",
            "prompt": "What was the earliest official ruling dynasty of China?",
            "correct_answer": "Qin"
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "prompt": "Which of these did not happen under the Qin dynasty?",
            "options": [
                "The Terracotta Army was made.",
                "Work began on the Great Wall.",
                "A single national script was created.",
                "The first Asian superhighway was created.",
                "The Silk Road was established."
            ],
            "correct_answer": "The Silk Road was established."
        },
        {
            "type": "short_answer",
            "prompt": "Whose maps led to the making of the Silk Road?",
            "correct_answer": "Zhang Qian"
        },
        {
            "type": "short_answer",
            "prompt": "When was the Silk Road created?",
            "correct_answer": "125BC"
        },
        {
            "type": "short_answer",
            "prompt": "Who developed paper?",
            "correct_answer": "Cai Lun"
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "prompt": "Which of these did Xu Shen write?",
            "options": [
                "The first Chinese dictionary.",
                "The first book of Chinese history.",
                "The first book of Chinese philosophy.",
                "The first collection of Chinese poems.",
                "The first textbook in China."
            ],
            "correct_answer": "The first Chinese dictionary."
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "prompt": "Which of these did Sima Qian write?",
            "options": [
                "The first Chinese dictionary.",
                "The first book of Chinese history.",
                "The first book of Chinese philosophy.",
                "The first collection of Chinese poems.",
                "The first textbook in China."
            ],
            "correct_answer": "The first book of Chinese history."
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "prompt": "Which of these was NOT used by Chinese alchemists to make gunpowder?",
            "options": [
                "Charcoal",
                "Niter",
                "Phosphorus",
                "Saltpetre",
                "Sulphur"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "Phosphorus"
        },
        {
            "type": "short_answer",
            "prompt": "Under which dynasty was gunpowder first used in warfare?",
            "correct_answer": "Tang"
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "prompt": "What is the name of the earliest known printed book?",
            "options": [
                "The Bronze Sutra",
                "The Silver Sutra",
                "The Gold Sutra",
                "The Diamond Sutra",
                "The Jade Sutra"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "The Diamond Sutra"
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "prompt": "Which of these modern-day cities were NEVER in Kublai Khan's empire?",
            "options": [
                "Baghdad",
                "Delhi",
                "Kabul",
                "Kyiv",
                "Samarkand"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "Delhi"
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "prompt": "Which of these events did not happen during Kublai Khan's reign?",
            "options": [
                "The first Muslims came.",
                "Paper money was introduced.",
                "Japan was conquered.",
                "A class system was introduced.",
                "Europeans were appointed as diplomats."
            ],
            "correct_answer": "Japan was conquered."
        },
        {
            "type": "short_answer",
            "prompt": "Under which dynasty could Chinese merchants first trade to other countries?",
            "correct_answer": "Ming"
        },
        {
            "type": "short_answer",
            "prompt": "Which Chinese general, known internationally as Koxinga, seized Taiwan in the Ming Dynasty?",
            "correct_answer": "Zheng Chenggong"
        },
        {
            "type": "short_answer",
            "prompt": "Under which dynasty was Taiwan annexed?",
            "correct_answer": "Qing"
        },
        {
            "type": "short_answer",
            "prompt": "What drug caused a war between the British and the Chinese?",
            "correct_answer": "Opium"
        },
        {
            "type": "short_answer",
            "prompt": "What is the densest city in China?",
            "correct_answer": "Macao"
        },
        {
            "type": "short_answer",
            "prompt": "What city was handed over to the British after the First Opium War?",
            "correct_answer": "Hong Kong"
        },
        {
            "type": "short_answer",
            "prompt": "Who, claiming he was the son of God, revolted against the Qing Dynasty?",
            "correct_answer": "Hong Xiuquan"
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "prompt": "For how long was the city of Nanjing under the control of the Taiping Rebellion?",
            "options": [
                "12 hours",
                "12 days",
                "12 weeks",
                "12 months",
                "12 years"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "12 years"
        }
    ]
}